Guide to the Equatorial Guinea Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Equatorial Guinea collection
1909-1999
1976-1998
MS 1514
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.77
(4 boxes)
The collection consists of printed material relating to politics and government in Equatorial Guinea and a photograph of two native women.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the African Collection Curator.
Associated Materials
African Collection (MS 605); Pamphlet Collection (MS 1351); African Postcard Collection (MS 1575). Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Arrangement
The papers are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of printed material relating to politics and government in Equatorial Guinea and a photograph of two native women.
Equatorial Guinea -- Politics and government; A.N.R.D
- Inventory, 1976
  - Alianza Nacional de Restauracion Democratica (ANRD): "La Voz del Pueblo", 1976 December (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Additional Material, 1909-1998; Accession 1998-M-016
  - Asociación para la Solidaridad Democrática con Guinea Ecuatorial (ASODEGUE), "Democracia para Guinea Ecuatorial", [1997] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Colegio Español de Malabo, "El Juego de la Paloma", 1996 January (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ebano, including a special edition for the birthday of President Obiang Nguema Mbasogo, 1986 June 5, 18, July 17, August 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Human rights statements from the United States government, articles from BBC News, CNN.com, and The New York Times, 1992 December 24, 1993 January 27, 1997 May 29, 1998 January 27, February 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ministerio de Economía y Comercio, "Rentas 2000," nos. 1-6, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Renta de las Personas Físicas (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Rusticas y Urbanas (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Sociedades (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cifra de Negocio Interior (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Timbre del Estado (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - La Persona Física (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ministerio de Planificación y Desarrollo Económico, Oficina Central de Censos, Resultados del II Censo de Población y II de Vivendas 1994, 1997 November (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Potopoto, nos. 14, 16, 18, 1985 November 30, 1986 March 31, June 28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Prisones Militares y Estado, document wherein Gaspar Roig y Peralta, prison administrator, requests transfer of prisoner Emilio Ripoll Sanchez, 1909 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Additional Material, 1926, 1999; Accession 2010-M-103
  - Profil La Guinée équatoriale, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of two women from Fernando Po, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Additional material, 1990s; Accession 2015-M-001
  - Printed material, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 1)